[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ CAN YOU HEAR THEM ♪
♪ THEY TALK ABOUT US ♪
♪ TELLING LIES ♪
♪ WELL, THAT'S NO SURPRISE ♪
♪ CAN YOU SEE THEM ♪
♪ SEE RIGHT THROUGH THEM ♪
♪ THEY HAVE NO SHIELD ♪
♪ NO SECRETS TO REVEAL ♪
♪ DOESN'T MATTER WHAT THEY SAY ♪
♪ IN THE JEALOUS
GAMES PEOPLE PLAY ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪
♪ THERE'S A WEAPON ♪
♪ THAT WE MUST USE ♪
♪ IN OUR DEFENSE ♪
♪ SILENCE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOOK AT THEM ♪
♪ LOOK RIGHT THROUGH THEM ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN
THEY'LL DISAPPEAR ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN WE'LL BE FEARED ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT THEY SAY ♪
♪ IN THE JEALOUS
GAMES PEOPLE PLAY ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪
♪ PAY NO MIND TO WHAT THEY SAY ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYWAY ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪
♪ HUSH, MY DARLING ♪
♪ DON'T YOU CRY ♪
♪ GUARDIAN ANGEL ♪
♪ FORGET THEIR LIES ♪
♪ CAN YOU HEAR THEM ♪
♪ THEY TALK ABOUT US ♪
♪ TELLING LIES ♪
♪ WELL, THAT'S NO SURPRISE ♪
♪ CAN YOU SEE THEM ♪
♪ SEE RIGHT THROUGH THEM ♪
♪ THEY HAVE NO SHIELD ♪
♪ NO SECRETS TO REVEAL ♪
♪ DOESN'T MATTER WHAT THEY SAY ♪
♪ IN THE JEALOUS
GAMES PEOPLE PLAY ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪
♪ PAY NO MIND TO WHAT THEY SAY ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYWAY ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪
♪ OH, OUR LIPS ARE SEALED ♪